<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>sant.rimcheats</packageId>
	<name>EasyRim - Overpowered Colony Enhancements</name>
	<author>Passion=Life</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>EasyRim is a deliberately overpowered RimWorld mod focused on stronger colonists, faster production, and better world-map mobility.

	CORE ENHANCEMENT SYSTEMS
	- Transcendence: cognitive, physical, biological, environmental, and psychic upgrades, plus adaptive armor and permanent nanite battle-morph tools.
	- Nano emergency reconstruction: the biological transcendence branch can prevent death and reconstruct critically wounded pawns after a delay.
	- Brave Soul, Blood Essence Resonance, and Pioneer Spirit: staged bonuses for combat, work, recovery, and survival.
	- Adaptive nexus spine: a craftable artificial spine that distributes enhancement branches and dynamically responds to health, combat, genes, and equipment.

	ABILITIES
	- Crimson Steel Infusion, Forbidden Restoration, Flesh Sculptor, Flesh Dissolution, Universal Bloodfeed, Eternal Revival.
	- Nano Disassembly Transit and Overmind Drops for rapid map/world-map mobility and tactical deployment.
	- Work Guidance and Colony Mobilization for powerful colony-wide tempo boosts.

	BUILDINGS AND PRODUCTION
	- Auto Drill: unattended deep-resource mining with sunlight checks, selectable power modes, and redeployable installation.
	- Buildable Life Support Unit: room pressurization/heating with substantial power output.
	- Batch components, neutroamine synthesis, synthread, and hyperweave crafting.

	ACCELERATED SYSTEMS AND BALANCE CHANGES
	- Faster biosculpter cycles, infinite chemreactor output, and wastepack atomization.
	- Greatly increased geothermal-generator and ship-reactor output.
	- Deep-resource detection for player-controlled tunneler mechs.

	Most character power is implemented through Hediffs and Abilities. TraitDef currently contains no gameplay entries.

	WARNING
	EasyRim is intentionally unbalanced and will significantly reduce the game's difficulty.
	AI-Assisted Mod: Developed with significant AI support, with human oversight and edits. Transparency note: Please avoid if you dislike AI-assisted creations.

	For RimWorld 1.6 (Odyssey).
	Steam Workshop: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3761671600
	GitHub: https://github.com/ledshic/easyrim
	Mod ID: 3761671600
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
