<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <crimsondynasty.label>&lt;color=#B22222&gt;crimson dynasty&lt;/color&gt;</crimsondynasty.label>
  <crimsondynasty.description>An awakened hemogenic lineage sustains predator, hemogenic, mesmer, and dreadguard channels at all times. Blood resonance is additionally granted only when the host carries the Hemogenic gene, and its stage adjusts dynamically with current blood state. Linked effects switch with state: bloodfrenzy at 45% or lower health in combat, noble poise above 80% health out of combat, and duelist ascendancy during melee engagements.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty.description>
  <crimsondynasty_predator.label>predator grace</crimsondynasty_predator.label>
  <crimsondynasty_predator.description>Predatory reflexes grant fast closes, clean strikes, and precise body control.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_predator.description>
  <crimsondynasty_hemogenic.label>hemogenic vigor</crimsondynasty_hemogenic.label>
  <crimsondynasty_hemogenic.description>Blood chemistry turns preternaturally efficient, accelerating recovery and resistance.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_hemogenic.description>
  <crimsondynasty_mesmer.label>mesmeric authority</crimsondynasty_mesmer.label>
  <crimsondynasty_mesmer.description>A cold aristocratic presence unsettles rivals and compels obedience in conversation.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_mesmer.description>
  <crimsondynasty_dreadguard.label>dreadguard resilience</crimsondynasty_dreadguard.label>
  <crimsondynasty_dreadguard.description>Battle-hardened bloodline resilience dampens pain and keeps the host fighting through mortal wounds, but open flame remains dangerous.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_dreadguard.description>
  <crimsondynasty_bloodfrenzy.label>bloodfrenzy ascendant</crimsondynasty_bloodfrenzy.label>
  <crimsondynasty_bloodfrenzy.description>At the edge of death, hunger and terror collapse into a monstrous battle crescendo.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_bloodfrenzy.description>
  <crimsondynasty_noble_poise.label>noble poise</crimsondynasty_noble_poise.label>
  <crimsondynasty_noble_poise.description>When well-fed and unpressured, aristocratic control sharpens social coercion and colony-level command.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_noble_poise.description>
  <crimsondynasty_duelist_ascendancy.label>duelist ascendancy</crimsondynasty_duelist_ascendancy.label>
  <crimsondynasty_duelist_ascendancy.description>Melee engagement unlocks predatory duelist routines focused on pressure and execution.

-- easyrim</crimsondynasty_duelist_ascendancy.description>
  <crimson_bloodrush_surge.label>bloodrush surge</crimson_bloodrush_surge.label>
  <crimson_bloodrush_surge.description>The lineage is forcibly overdriven into a frenzy state. Lethality and speed explode, while restraint vanishes.

-- easyrim</crimson_bloodrush_surge.description>
  <crimson_sovereign_gaze_marked.label>sovereign gaze marked</crimson_sovereign_gaze_marked.label>
  <crimson_sovereign_gaze_marked.description>The target's will falters under predatory authority, reducing coordination and resistance.

-- easyrim</crimson_sovereign_gaze_marked.description>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.label>blood hemogen resonance</bloodhemogen_resonance.label>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.description>The host's vitality rises and falls with hemogen reserves. When hemogen is plentiful, the body surges with strength; when depleted, weakness and pain follow.

-- easyrim</bloodhemogen_resonance.description>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.0.label>hemogen peak</bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.0.label>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.1.label>hemogen rich</bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.1.label>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.2.label>hemogen balanced</bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.2.label>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.3.label>hemogen lacking</bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.3.label>
  <bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.4.label>hemogen depleted</bloodhemogen_resonance.stages.4.label>
  <EM_CrimsonSpine_SanguineAscendancy.label>sanguine ascendancy</EM_CrimsonSpine_SanguineAscendancy.label>
  <EM_CrimsonSpine_SanguineAscendancy.description>When blood resonance stays in the high band, the implanted dynasty spine pushes each movement and strike into a predatory peak cadence.

-- easyrim</EM_CrimsonSpine_SanguineAscendancy.description>

  <EM_CrimsonDynastySpine.label>crimson dynasty spine</EM_CrimsonDynastySpine.label>
  <EM_CrimsonDynastySpine.labelNoun>a crimson dynasty spine</EM_CrimsonDynastySpine.labelNoun>
  <EM_CrimsonDynastySpine.description>This spine keeps predator grace and hemogenic vigor as a baseline, then grants blood resonance only when the host carries the Hemogenic gene, with resonance stage adjusting dynamically to current blood state. Linked effects split by state: bloodfrenzy below 45% health in combat, noble poise above 80% health out of combat, duelist ascendancy during melee engagements, and sanguine ascendancy while resonance remains in the high range.

-- easyrim</EM_CrimsonDynastySpine.description>
</LanguageData>
