<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <corsaircreed.label>&lt;color=#B7410E&gt;corsair creed&lt;/color&gt;</corsaircreed.label>
  <corsaircreed.description>The corsair doctrine permanently maintains boarding, gunnery, scavenging, and blackflag aggression modules, then layers active abilities for burst windows. Linked effects react to combat state: ranged exchanges lock deck gunnery posture, while health at 45% or lower in combat triggers marauder frenzy.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed.description>
  <corsaircreed_boarder.label>boarding momentum</corsaircreed_boarder.label>
  <corsaircreed_boarder.description>Close-quarters boarding drills amplify speed, control, and brutal follow-through.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed_boarder.description>
  <corsaircreed_gunner.label>deck gunner's eye</corsaircreed_gunner.label>
  <corsaircreed_gunner.description>Predatory timing and recoil control sharpen ranged lethality.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed_gunner.description>
  <corsaircreed_scavenger.label>wreck scavenger instinct</corsaircreed_scavenger.label>
  <corsaircreed_scavenger.description>Loot-minded reflexes improve hauling, stripping, and rapid battlefield recovery.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed_scavenger.description>
  <corsaircreed_blackflag.label>blackflag audacity</corsaircreed_blackflag.label>
  <corsaircreed_blackflag.description>A raider's nerve dulls fear and pain, keeping the host aggressive when others would fold.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed_blackflag.description>
  <corsaircreed_gunner_posture.label>deck gunnery posture</corsaircreed_gunner_posture.label>
  <corsaircreed_gunner_posture.description>The host enters a stabilized gunnery stance during live exchanges, sacrificing subtlety for relentless ranged pressure.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed_gunner_posture.description>
  <corsaircreed_marauder_frenzy.label>marauder frenzy</corsaircreed_marauder_frenzy.label>
  <corsaircreed_marauder_frenzy.description>At critical health in close battle, the corsair doctrine abandons restraint and forces a lethal surge.

-- easyrim</corsaircreed_marauder_frenzy.description>
  <corsair_broadside_overdrive.label>broadside overdrive</corsair_broadside_overdrive.label>
  <corsair_broadside_overdrive.description>An all-in firing rhythm tuned for short violent exchanges. Accuracy cadence rises, but exposure risk increases.

-- easyrim</corsair_broadside_overdrive.description>
  <corsair_cutthroat_rush.label>cutthroat rush</corsair_cutthroat_rush.label>
  <corsair_cutthroat_rush.description>The host commits to a savage boarding sprint. Pursuit and close-range lethality spike at the cost of tactical exposure.

-- easyrim</corsair_cutthroat_rush.description>
  <corsair_plunder_marked.label>marked for plunder</corsair_plunder_marked.label>
  <corsair_plunder_marked.description>The target is highlighted as easy loot, disrupting footing and composure under fire.

-- easyrim</corsair_plunder_marked.description>
  <EM_CorsairSpine.label>blackflag spineframe</EM_CorsairSpine.label>
  <EM_CorsairSpine.labelNoun>a blackflag spineframe</EM_CorsairSpine.labelNoun>
  <EM_CorsairSpine.description>This spine keeps gunner discipline and scavenger instinct active as the corsair baseline. Linked effects escalate with combat tempo: boarding momentum during combat, deck gunnery posture in ranged exchanges, marauder frenzy below 45% health in combat, and blackflag audacity while drafted.

-- easyrim</EM_CorsairSpine.description>
</LanguageData>
